A Guide to the Records of the Charlottesville School Board 1869-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Facilities Management
  - A. Correspondence
    - Correspondence Superintendent James G. Johnson and architect Charles J. Calrow 1931 April-June, 50 items (Box-folder 13:3)
      Correspondents include W. L. Lacy, The Wilson Company, Charlottesville Hardware Company, Jarman's Inc., Virginia School Supply Company, E. C. Barnett, W. L. Lacy, Wallace Johnson, C. J. Davis, W. R. Smith, and Brown & Taylor. Topics include plumbing work at McGuffey School; inspection of Clark School; settlement from Failes-Burrage; minutes of a special meeting about concerns related to the bidding process for construction of Clark School; receipts and itemized annual statements from Calrow.
    - Oversize sketches of Lanterns, 2 items
    - Correspondence Superintendent James G. Johnson about facilities management issues 1932, 37 items (Box-folder 13:4)
      Correspondents mentioned are J. A. Burgess, Failes-Burrage Construction Company, Barnes Lumber Corporation, J. L. Dettor & Son, Charlottesville Lumber Company, and W. L. Lacy, Hugh L. Sulfridge, E. V. Walker, Fred L. Watson, and board members, Robert A. Watson, John P. Sneed, Mrs. Charles A. Lambert, Mrs. Charles A. Graves, B. Lee Hawkins, F. B. Peyton, Miss Gertrude C. Mann, A. G. A. Balz and M. Kaufman. Topics included are budget; salaries; School Board minutes; repairs, cleaning and painting for Midway, Venable, McGuffey, and Jefferson School Buildings. Of note is that a "white" teacher earned twenty thousand dollars while a "colored" teacher earned four thousand dollars.
    - Correspondence Superintendent James G. Johnson about facilities management issues 1937, 13 items (Box-folder 13:5)
      Correspondents included are W. L. Lacy, W. M. Bailey, E. C. Barnett, Hanckel-Citizens Insurance Corporation, H. B. Smith Company, Greaver and Roberts Repair Shop, and the Charlottesville Supply Company. Topics include bids for plumbing work at Midway and the contract awarded to W. L. Lacy.
    - Correspondence Superintendent James G. Johnson about construction for Lane High School 1939, 32 items (Box-folder 13:6)
      Correspondents included are Pendleton S. Clark, W. L. Lacy, E. H. Sheldon and Company, Ezekiel Weilman Company, American Seating Company, Southern Desk Company, and Ritchie Electric Company. Topics mentioned are contractors; furniture and equipment contracts and specifications with the Federal Works Agency; minutes of the School Board; bidding instructions; cost estimates; and bids. (needs flattening)
    - Oversize drawings of Lane High School by Pendleton S. Clark and land grant and sketch of plat from the City of Charlottesville to the Charlottesville School Board for playground 1944, 12 items
    - Correspondence Superintendent James G. Johnson and Pendleton S. Clark about the construction of Lane 1940 January-May, 45 items (Box-folder 13:7)
      Correspondents included are Pendleton S. Clark, Ezekiel & Weilman Company, Inc; James I. Barnes Construction Company; American Seating Company; Berger Manufacturing Division; E. H. Sheldon & Company; Baughman Stationery Company; Knoxville Scenic Studios; Flowers School Equipment Company; and The Southern Desk Company. Topics mentioned are blue prints for the kitchen and library and other construction for Lane High School.
    - Oversize notebook (E. C. Sheldon) with sketches of kitchen equipment by Pendleton S. Clark
  - B. Specifications and contract documents
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents Dr. Johnson & Pendleton S. Clark for Lane High School 1939 February, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents Dr. Johnson & Pendleton S. Clark for Lane High School 1939, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:2)
    - 3 Facilities Management Contract Documents and catalogs for Lane High School 1939 August, 1 notebook and 2 catalogs (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents and catalogs for Lane High School 1939 August, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents with American Seating Company (Lane High School) 1940 January-April, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents for equipment with American Seating Company (Lane High School) 1940, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents with Knoxville Scenic Studios (auditorium and stage equipment for Lane) 1940 January-April, 1 notebook (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Facilities Management Contract Documents with Ritchie Electric Company (for Lane) 1940 January, 1 notebook (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Facilities Management Court Case School Board payment 1915, 1 item (Box-folder 15:2)
      There are handwritten notes about the court's decision that the School Board did not have to make payment to William Hodges.
    - Facilities Management payments to the Wilson Company 1930-1931, 13 items (Box-folder 15:3)
      Certificates for payment
    - Facilities Management specifications for equipment (Lane High School) 1939-1940, 1 notebook (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Facilities Management specifications contracts for equipment (Lane High School) 1940, 2 notebooks (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Facilities Management specifications contracts with Flowers School Equipment Company and Knoxville Scenic Studios (Lane High School) 1940, 2 notebooks (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Facilities Management Specifications for Equipment for Flowers School Equipment Company 1940, 1 notebook (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Facilities Management Supplies 1922-1923, 38 items (Box-folder 15:8)
      Correspondents include W. T. Martin Hardware, The Hall's Safe Company, M. C. Thomas Furniture Company, National Seating Company, Progressive Teacher, Steel Furniture Company, Virginia Penitentiary Industrial Department, The Elastic Tip company, and The Peabody School Furniture Company. There are estimates and brochures for desks and other school supplies (for Venable School).
    - Facilities Management Supplies 1924-1925, 121 items (Box-folder 15:9)
      Correspondents included are Virginia School Supply Company, Virginia Penitentiary Industrial Department, Southern School Supply Company, General Seating Company, The Theodor Kundtz Company, E. H. Sheldon & Company, West Virginia Seating Company, ACME Chair Company, Keystone View Company, A. H. Andrews Company, Great Northern Chair Company. There is also information and samples from other suppliers such as Cunningham Springless Shade Company, A. Flanagan Company, Jarman Book Company, E. W. A. Rowles Company, Practical Drawing Company, Beckley-Cardy Company School Furnishers, A. J. Nystrom & Company, King Lumber Company, and Funk & Wagnalls Company. There is information about ordering and receiving desks and other school supplies for Venable and Midway schools.
    - Facilities Management Supplies 1926-1926, 45 items (Box-folder 16:1)
      Correspondents E. H. Sheldon, R. L. Thomas Company, Inc.,The Johnson Service Company, Virginia School Supply Company, The Theodor Kundtz Company, Virginia Penitentiary Industrial Department, Spencer Lens Company, Cary Manufacturing Company, ACME Chair Company, American Seating Company, National School Equipment, Great Northern Chair Company, and The A. H. Andrews Company. There are orders, catalogs, and quotations for school supplies including a lavatory, and an electric heat pump for McGuffey School.
    - Facilities Management Supplies (coal, blackboards, safes etc…) 1934-1935, 42 items (Box-folder 16:2)
      The Harding Supply Co., The Thrift Coal Company, Valentine and Hull, Wood, Vest & Company, Burnley Brothers, Margarette Coal Company, Frances Coal Company, Divisional Code Authority, J. J. Porter Coal Company, Draper Sight-Saving Window Shades, and Sargent & Greenleaf, Inc. Hall's Safe Co.
    - Facilities Management notes on construction projects n. d., 15 items (Box-folder 16:3)
- Series V Financial
  - Financial Applications for books 1897-1898, 3 groups of applications (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Financial Application for books 1898 need flattening, 100 applications (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Financial Applications for books 1900 need flattening, 100 items (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Financial Bank books and miscellaneous 1915-1933; n. d., 30 items (Box-folder 16:7)
    There is information about the Perry Foundation for grants and an income tax form.
  - Financial bank deposits 1959 June-December, 11 items (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Financial bank statements 1960 January-June, 12 items (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Financial bank statements 1961 June-November, 9 items (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Financial bank statements 1961 November-1962 May, 12 items (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Financial bank statements 1962 June-December, 6 items (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Financial bank statements Deposit slips 1962 September-December, 4 items (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Financial bank statements 1963 January-July, 13 items (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Financial bank statements 1965 June-December, 5 items (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Financial bank statements 1966 January-June, 6 items (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Financial bank statements 1967 June-January, 8 items (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Financial bank statements 1968 January-December, 11 items (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Financial bank statements 1969, 13 items (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Financial bank Statements 1970 January-December, 12 items (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Financial bank statements 1971 January-June, 6 items (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Financial check stubs 1939-1945, 1 notebook (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Financial check stubs 1945-1947, 1 notebook (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Financial check stubs 1947-1948 February-October, 1 notebook (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Financial check stubs 1948-1950, 1 notebook (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Financial check stubs 1950-1951, 1 notebook (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Financial check stubs 1951-1953 January-April, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Financial check stubs 1953-1954 May-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Financial check stubs 1954-1956 December-November, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Financial check stubs 1956-1959 December-May, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Financial check stubs 1959-1961 May-October, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Financial check stubs 1965-1968, 1 notebook (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Financial check stubs 1969-1971 January-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Financial check stubs 1971-1972 January-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Financial expenditures 1954-1955, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Financial expenditures 1954-1955, notebook 2 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Financial expenditures 1956-1957, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Financial expenditures 1956-1957, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Financial expenditures 1956-1957, notebook pt 3 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Financial expenditures 1957-1958, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Financial expenditures 1957-1958, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Financial expenditures 1958-1959, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Financial expenditures 1958-1959, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Financial expenditures 1960-1961, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Financial expenditures 1960-1961, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Financial expenditures 1961-1962, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Financial expenditures 1961-1962, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Financial expenditures 1961-1962, notebook pt 3 (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Financial expenditures 1962-1963, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Financial expenditures 1962-1963, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Financial expenditures 1963-1964, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Financial expenditures 1963-1964, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Financial expenditures 1963-1964, notebook (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Financial expenditures 1964-1965, notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Financial expenditures 1964-1965, notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Financial expenditure Ledger 1904-1920, 1 ledger (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Financial expenditure loose pages 1904-1920, 13 items (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1912-1915, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1915 July-1917 November, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1917 December-1920 February, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1920 March-1922 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1922 July-1924 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1924-July-1926 March, 1 ledger (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1926 April-1927 November, 1 ledger (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1927 December-1929 November, 1 ledger (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1929 December- 1931 October, 1 ledger (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1931 November-1933 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1933-1935, 1 ledger (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1935 July-1937 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1937 July-1939 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1940 October 31-1946 June, 1 ledger-McGuffey with some pages torn out (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1940 October 31-1946 June, 1 ledger-McGuffey (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1946 July-1949 May, 1 ledger (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1946 July-1959 January, 1 ledger-McGuffey (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Financial expenditures ledger 1949-1952, 1 ledger (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Financial expenditure ledger 1949 August-1953 June, 1 ledger-McGuffey (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Financial expenditures ledger 1953 July-1963 July, 1 ledger (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Financial expenditures ledger 1958 July-1963 June, 1 ledger (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Financial expenditures ledger 1970-1971, 20 ledger pages-McGuffey. Items in this box are in very bad condition. (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Financial expenditures ledger 1972-1973, 20 ledger pages-Buford. Items in this box are in very bad condition. (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Financial expenditures ledger n. d., 50 ledger pages-Buford. Items in this box are in very bad condition. (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Financial invoices (bills) from vendors for services rendered to the schools 1922-1942, 77 items (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Financial invoices 1924; 1929-1933, 30 items (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Financial invoices 1953 October-1954 July, 94 items (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Financial invoices 1954 August, 51 items (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Financial invoices 1954 September, 54 items (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Financial invoices 1954 October, 96 items (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Financial invoices 1954 November-December, 122 items (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Financial invoices 1955 January, 91 items (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Financial invoices 1955 February, 59 items (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Financial invoices 1955 March, 89 items (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Financial invoices 1955 April, 55 items (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Financial invoices 1955 May, 5 items (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Financial invoices 1955 June, 47 items very dirty (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Financial invoices 1955 July, 60 items very dirty (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Financial invoices 1955 August, 52 items very dirty (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Financial invoices 1955 September, 94 items very dirty (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Financial invoices 1955 October, 75 items (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Financial invoices 1955 November, 84 items (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Financial invoices 1955 December, 70 items (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Financial invoices 1956 January, 56 items (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Financial invoices 1956 February, 63 items (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Financial invoices 1956 March-April, 67 items (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Financial invoices 1956 May, 70 items (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Financial invoices 1956 June-July, 49 items (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Financial invoices 1956 August, 68 items (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Financial invoices 1956 September, 68 items (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Financial invoices 1956 October, 85 items (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Financial invoices 1956 November, 96 items (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Financial invoices 1956 December, 62 items (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Financial invoices 1957 January-February, 123 items (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Financial invoices 1957 March-April, 128 items (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Financial invoices 1957 May-June, 77 items (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Financial invoices 1957 August-September, 30 items (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Financial invoices 1957 October-1958, 71 items (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Financial invoices 1959 January-September, 110 items (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Financial invoices 1959 October-December, 42 items (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Financial invoices 1960 January-April, 48 items (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Financial invoices 1960 May-June, 32 items (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Financial invoices 1961, 46 items (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Financial invoices 1962 January-June, 51 items (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Financial invoices 1962 July-December, 47 items (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Financial invoices 1963 January-June, 74 items (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders 1965-1966, 55 items (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders 1967, 88 items (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders 1968-1969, 111 items (Box-folder 36:5)
  - Financial invoices 1969, 118 items (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Financial invoices Buford Junior High School 1970-1971, 130 items (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders Buford Junior High School 1971-1972 July, 68 items (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders Buford Junior High School 1972 August-December, 73 items (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders Buford Junior High School 1973 January-February, 59 items (Box-folder 37:4)
  - Financial invoices and purchase orders Buford Junior High School 1973 March-June, 78 items (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Financial invoices n. d., 5 items (Box-folder 37:6)
  - Financial invoices for state programs 1965-1966, 30 items (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Financial invoices for state programs 1966-1967, 21 items (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Financial invoices for state programs 1967-1968, 6 items (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Financial invoices for state programs 1968-1969, 5 items (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Financial invoices for state programs 1969-1979, 51 items (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Financial invoices for Title I 1968, 36 items (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Financial payroll teacher's salaries 1905-1911, 40 items (Box-folder 38:7)
    Restricted due to social security numbers.
  - Financial payroll teacher's salaries 1909-1913, 1 ledger (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1954 July-October, 12 items (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1954 November-December, 10 items (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1955 January-March, 23 items (Box-folder 39:2)
    Includes correspondence between teacher, Marion Trevillion and Fendall R. Ellis about tutoring adults and their progress and travel receipts.
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1955 April-July, 1 notebook Needs flattening and cleaning subdivided into 3a. (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1955 August-October, notebook pt 1 Needs flattening and cleaning (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and other 1955 November-December, 1 notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 40:1)
    Included are invoices for reimbursements of teachers collecting census information. Restricted due to social security numbers.
  - Financial Payroll teachers and other 1956 January-March, 1 notebook pt 3 (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Financial Payroll teachers and other 1956 April-May, 1 notebook pt 4 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Financial Payroll teachers and other 1956 July-August, 1 notebook pt 5 (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1956 September-October, 1 notebook (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1956 November-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1957 January-June, 1 notebook (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1957 July-August, 1 notebook (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1957 September-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers miscellaneous 1957, 4 items (Box-folder 41:4)
    Included are travel reimbursements and insurance information. Restricted due to social security numbers.
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1958 January-March, 1 notebook (Box-folder 41:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1958 April-June, 1 notebook (Box-folder 41:6)
    Restricted due to social security numbers
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1959 July-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1960 January-April, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:2)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1960 May-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1961 January-May, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1961 June-September, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers Quarterly Report of Wages Paid 1959-1961, 1 notebook (Box-folder 42:6)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1963 May-September, 1 notebook (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1963 October-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 43:2)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1964 January-March, 1 notebook (Box-folder 43:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1964 April-August, 1 notebook (Box-folder 43:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1964 September-October, 1 notebook (Box-folder 43:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1964 November-December, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 January-February, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 March-May, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 June, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 July-August, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 September-October, 1 notebook (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1965 November-December, notebook (Box-folder 45:1)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1966 January-March, 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:2)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1966 April-May, 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:3)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others 1966 June-August, 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:4)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others n. d., 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:5)
  - Financial payroll teachers and others n. d., 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:6)
    Employee coding tickets with social security numbers. Restricted due to social security numbers.
  - Financial payroll teachers and others n. d., 1 notebook (Box-folder 45:7)
  - Oversize Financial payroll teachers and others n. d.; [1964-1966], 100 items
  - Financial receipts 1934-1939, 1 notebook (Box-folder 46:1)
    These are standardized receipts for school payments.
  - Financial receipts 1954 July-August, 1 notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 46:2)
  - Financial receipts 1954 September-October, 1 notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 46:3)
  - Financial receipts 1954 November-December, 1 notebook pt 3 (Box-folder 46:4)
  - Financial receipts 1954-1955 December-January, 1 notebook pt 4 (Box-folder 46:5)
  - Financial receipts 1955 January-March, 1 notebook pt 5 (Box-folder 46:6)
  - Financial receipts 1955 March-May, 1 notebook pt 6 (Box-folder 47:1)
  - Financial receipts 1955 May-June, 1 notebook pt 7 (Box-folder 47:2)
  - Financial receipts 1956 July-September, 1 notebook pt 1 (Box-folder 47:3)
  - Financial receipts 1956 October-November, 1 notebook pt 2 (Box-folder 47:4)